Well, the crawler has finished doing its job.
We see three table changes here.
We go back to databases and go to our mission DH database,
and we see our three aggregated tables
right here, in fact, okay?
So what we can do is we can go do, um,
from here in Roth know, and uh, right click on that, the tab
and scroll down.
The database is already chosen here as Mission, mission dh.
Okay, now we see, we have, we see the three tables
that we wanted to see that aggregated tables.
So what's the next step? Next step is to kind
of do our unit testing
before we hand this over to the data analyst, right?
And we go back to our mapping sheet
and we see that this is the logic here.
We are gonna fire our queries,
fire our queries on these different tables
and do our checks.
So for example, first we to do a preview table
and look at the data and uh, query has been fired
and we see some data sets here, in fact, okay,
results set is right here, in fact.
So unit testing is a part of the development.
It is something that, you know, you just tell
to the recruiters
or to the hiring manager that okay, yes, at the bar,
my roles and responsibilities were to, you know,
develop my data engineering pipelines per the mapping sheet
given to me and also
to unit test the data loaded by my pipelines.
That's pretty much it. Okay.
That is what you need to remember from the
interview perspective.
The whole intent is to make sure that
whatever code you have built, you know, does its job
per the mapping speed mapping specification.
And remember, data analysts would also be testing
the data that you have loaded.
I mean, it's not just that you'll be testing,
you are doing your urine testing,
but they will be doing a lot more thorough testing
because they'll be building the reports based on this data.
So their testing would be a lot, lot more detailed.
And when they do their testing, they might find issues
and they'll come back to you
or they might update, uh, this mapping sheet
and they may add some more table tables here, whatever.
So this is how the typical development last cycle happens.
And if they change the requirements, yeah,
you'll go back and change your code.
If they find an issue in the data you have loaded,
they'll let you know and you'll then look at the
code and you'll fix it.
And then finally you'll let them know,
okay, we have fixed the code.
Take a look at the data again, they'll do the testing again.
Finally, when it's all good, you go to the next steps.
That, that's the typical data engineering, uh,
development life cycle.
And the next steps would be to also think about how
to really automate this entire pipeline.
So far we've been just doing this manually, right?
It's in development. How do you then kind of move it
to the test environment
and then to the production environment?
These are different things that are typically part
of your development lifecycle.
And again, just so that I
Don't forget, so these tables access may not be
provided initially to the data analyst.
And so you'll send an email to cloud engineer team, say,
Hey, I have cleared this new tables, provide access to data
to the data analyst team.